{
  "user": [
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/150?img=68",
      "id": "p0",
      "name": "John Smith",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": [
        {
          "user": {
            "id": "p3",
            "name": "Gertrude Boyle",
            "avatar": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p3"
          },
          "answer": [
            {
              "question": "How much do you trust this person to deliver high quality work?",
              "answer": 6
            },
            {
              "question": "Is this person up to date with the latest accounting regulations?",
              "answer": "Not fully. You should work on trying to stay more up to date with regulations"
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand the technical domain of our product?",
              "answer": 6
            },
            {
              "question": "Have there been any situations where this person could have managed their emotions better? What happened?",
              "answer": "sadfas"
            },
            {
              "question": "Does this person care about our users and treats customer support as a high priority?",
              "answer": "Not always - you should work on this aspect"
            },
            {
              "question": "What would you like this person to work on the most during the next month, to enable their continued growth?",
              "answer": "asfasdfa"
            },
            {
              "question": "How transparent and clear are this person's plans and work tasks?",
              "answer": "I almost always know what you are working on, but not always the details or next steps, only the outcomes you are after."
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand our business goals and roadmap?",
              "answer": 3
            },
            {
              "question": "Is there anything else you'd like to share with this person?",
              "answer": "sdfaf"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "user": {
            "id": "p6",
            "name": "Jai Malone",
            "avatar": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p6"
          },
          "answer": [
            {
              "question": "How much do you trust this person to deliver high quality work?",
              "answer": 5
            },
            {
              "question": "Is this person up to date with the latest accounting regulations?",
              "answer": "Not fully. You should work on trying to stay more up to date with regulations"
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand the technical domain of our product?",
              "answer": 8
            },
            {
              "question": "Have there been any situations where this person could have managed their emotions better? What happened?",
              "answer": "asdfasf"
            },
            {
              "question": "Does this person care about our users and treats customer support as a high priority?",
              "answer": "Yes, you go out of our way to help our users and improve their experience"
            },
            {
              "question": "What would you like this person to work on the most during the next month, to enable their continued growth?",
              "answer": "sadfasf"
            },
            {
              "question": "How transparent and clear are this person's plans and work tasks?",
              "answer": "I almost always know what you are working on, but not always the details or next steps, only the outcomes you are after."
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand our business goals and roadmap?",
              "answer": 10
            },
            {
              "question": "Is there anything else you'd like to share with this person?",
              "answer": "afsafew"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "user": {
            "id": "p1",
            "name": "Martha Liberty",
            "avatar": "https://i.pravatar.cc/150?img=48"
          },
          "answer": [
            {
              "question": "How much do you trust this person to deliver high quality work?",
              "answer": 5
            },
            {
              "question": "Is this person up to date with the latest accounting regulations?",
              "answer": "Not fully. You should work on trying to stay more up to date with regulations"
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand the technical domain of our product?",
              "answer": 7
            },
            {
              "question": "Have there been any situations where this person could have managed their emotions better? What happened?",
              "answer": "skipped"
            },
            {
              "question": "Does this person care about our users and treats customer support as a high priority?",
              "answer": "Not always - you should work on this aspect"
            },
            {
              "question": "What would you like this person to work on the most during the next month, to enable their continued growth?",
              "answer": "asdfa"
            },
            {
              "question": "How transparent and clear are this person's plans and work tasks?",
              "answer": "I almost always know what you are working on, but not always the details or next steps, only the outcomes you are after."
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand our business goals and roadmap?",
              "answer": 10
            },
            {
              "question": "Is there anything else you'd like to share with this person?",
              "answer": "skipped"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/150?img=48",
      "id": "p1",
      "name": "Martha Liberty",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p2",
      "id": "p2",
      "name": "Persephone Woodley",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p3",
      "id": "p3",
      "name": "Gertrude Boyle",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": [
        {
          "user": {
            "id": "p0",
            "name": "John Smith",
            "avatar": "https://i.pravatar.cc/150?img=68"
          },
          "answer": [
            {
              "question": "How much do you trust this person to deliver high quality work?",
              "answer": 4
            },
            {
              "question": "Is this person up to date with the latest accounting regulations?",
              "answer": "Not fully. You should work on trying to stay more up to date with regulations"
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand the technical domain of our product?",
              "answer": 5
            },
            {
              "question": "Have there been any situations where this person could have managed their emotions better? What happened?",
              "answer": "skipped"
            },
            {
              "question": "Does this person care about our users and treats customer support as a high priority?",
              "answer": "Yes, you go out of our way to help our users and improve their experience"
            },
            {
              "question": "What would you like this person to work on the most during the next month, to enable their continued growth?",
              "answer": "sfasfaes"
            },
            {
              "question": "How transparent and clear are this person's plans and work tasks?",
              "answer": "I almost always know what you are working on, but not always the details or next steps, only the outcomes you are after."
            },
            {
              "question": "How well does this person understand our business goals and roadmap?",
              "answer": 7
            },
            {
              "question": "Is there anything else you'd like to share with this person?",
              "answer": "skipped"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/150?img=53",
      "id": "p4",
      "name": "Bertram Patton",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p5",
      "id": "p5",
      "name": "Camron Devlin",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p6",
      "id": "p6",
      "name": "Jai Malone",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p7",
      "id": "p7",
      "name": "Ember Mcmillan",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p8",
      "id": "p8",
      "name": "Jeanette Hume",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "id": "p9",
      "name": "Harold Hays",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    },
    {
      "avatarUrl": "https://i.pravatar.cc/100?u=p11",
      "id": "p10",
      "name": "Anna-Marie Orr",
      "myFeedbacks": [],
      "teamfeedbacks": []
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "q1",
      "type": "scale",
      "required": true,
      "label": "How much do you trust this person to deliver high quality work?"
    },
    {
      "id": "q2",
      "type": "multipleChoice",
      "required": true,
      "label": "Is this person up to date with the latest accounting regulations?",
      "options": [
        {
          "value": 1,
          "label": "Not fully. You should work on trying to stay more up to date with regulations"
        },
        {
          "value": 2,
          "label": "Yes, you are reasonably up to date with new regulations."
        },
        {
          "value": 3,
          "label": "Yes, you are the one I look up to when I need information about new regulations"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "q3",
      "type": "scale",
      "required": true,
      "label": "How well does this person understand the technical domain of our product?"
    },
    {
      "id": "q4",
      "type": "text",
      "required": false,
      "label": "Have there been any situations where this person could have managed their emotions better? What happened?"
    },
    {
      "id": "q5",
      "type": "multipleChoice",
      "required": true,
      "label": "Does this person care about our users and treats customer support as a high priority?",
      "options": [
        {
          "value": 1,
          "label": "Not always - you should work on this aspect"
        },
        {
          "value": 2,
          "label": "Yes, you go out of our way to help our users and improve their experience"
        },
        {
          "value": 3,
          "label": "Yes, your understanding of our users and the empathy you demonstrate is second to none"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "q6",
      "type": "text",
      "required": true,
      "label": "What would you like this person to work on the most during the next month, to enable their continued growth?"
    },
    {
      "id": "q7",
      "type": "multipleChoice",
      "required": true,
      "label": "How transparent and clear are this person's plans and work tasks?",
      "options": [
        {
          "value": 1,
          "label": "I frequently not know what you are working on, please work with me to raise visibility"
        },
        {
          "value": 2,
          "label": "I almost always know what you are working on, but not always the details or next steps, only the outcomes you are after."
        },
        {
          "value": 3,
          "label": "Your plans are clear and readily available to those around you, and I always know what the next step is."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "q8",
      "type": "scale",
      "required": true,
      "label": "How well does this person understand our business goals and roadmap?"
    },
    {
      "id": "q9",
      "type": "text",
      "required": false,
      "label": "Is there anything else you'd like to share with this person?"
    }
  ]
}